# REGINALD F. SACKEY-ADDO

E-Mail address – fiifisackey.a@gmail.com | Phone Number – 214-436-6030 https://www.linkedin.com/in/reggiesackey | http://reggiesackey.co

### **EDUCATION**

- BA in Political Science, 2012-2016 (Grinnell College- Grinnell, IA) 3.2 GPA
- Vice President and Treasurer of African and Caribbean Student Union
- Winner of 2013 Grinnell College Startup Weekend
- Co-Leader of Social Entrepreneurs of Grinnell

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven, creative, technologically proficient professional fuses multi-platform web development experience and social media strategy with a strong background in entrepreneurship and digital marketing. Also proficient in research and data analysis, as well as providing high level customer support.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

- > Freelance Web Developer and Social Media Strategist (August 2016 Present)
  - Develop search engine optimized websites for dozens of small businesses in Dallas area
  - Run social media campaigns leading to over \$10,000 worth of sales
  - Plan and run successful inbound marketing campaigns (email, SEO, blogging, PPC)
  - Build and maintain robust ecommerce sites, capturing over \$300,000 in sales
  - Organized and broadcast client's healthcare conference to over a 1000 viewers worldwide
- ➤ Content Strategist at Visage Payroll (September 2016 May 2017)
  - Embarked on Growth Hacking projects to grow social media channels by hundreds of followers
  - Developed and implemented plans to optimize web pages, leading to 10% improvement in SEO rank
  - Conducted customer interviews to create marketing content, and also provide support and design recommendations
- > Co-Founder/Manager at Richard Golden Foods (September 2014–May 2016)
  - Founded and operated a food delivery service for the town of Grinnell, IA
  - Served as customer liaison, taking orders and providing excellent service to generate repeat business
  - Managed a team of 5 employees to consistently beat sales projections and generate about \$5000 in monthly revenue
- > Web Developer at Grinnell College Web Services (August 2013 August 2014)
  - Facilitated the transfer of gigabytes of data and multimedia content onto new website
  - Was responsible for solving hundreds of user submitted support tickets per week

### VOLUNTEER WORK

- Offered free services in marketing and communications to various local level political campaigns and causes in Collin County, Texas
- Catered at multiple fundraisers, helping to raise over \$10,000 for Mid Iowa Community Action, a charity which serves families plagued by poverty